Horlacher, John Arbitration Records 5587
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Dolly Madison Industries, Inc., Foods Division, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania vs. IBT, Local 869, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Issue: subcontracting (notes, briefs & exhibits).
- Dorr-Oliver, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge No. 1648, 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  1) Issue: contract interpretation - vacancies. 2) Issue: definitions - Job. 3) Issue: shift scheduling - shift transfers, temporary change, rates of pay. (includes notes, exhibits, agreements).
- Dovnington Paper Co. Cases, 1956-1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Dragon Cement Co., Division of Martin-Marietta Corp. Northampton Plant vs. The United Cement, Lime & Gypsum Workers. Int'l. Union, Local No. 26, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Issue: bargaining unit work
- 6DuPont De Nemours, E. I. and Co. vs. Chemical & Industrial Union, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Issue: call-in pay.
- Durez Plastics Division, Hooker Chemical Corp. vs. IAM, Lodge 2112 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Issue: discipline -discrimination, union activities & mbrsp. (+ supplemental opinion)
- Dynaco Co. vs. Machine Tool & Die Union, Local 155, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Issue: leaving plant v/o permission.
- Dynasil Corporation of America vs. Teamsters Local Union 676, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Issue: discharge - negligence, destruction of employers property. (includes notes, briefs & exhibits)
- Eastern Shore Public Service Co. vs. IBEW, Local 1307, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Issue: disability reinstatement
- Eaton Corp. Industrial Truck Division vs. IAM, Lodge 1717, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  1) Issue: discharge - fighting. 2) Issue: discharge - theft (includes notes, exhibits & agreement)
- Eaton Yale & Toune, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge No. 1717, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  1) Issue: discharge - intoxication. 2) Issue: discrimination - trainee - race. 3) Issue: assignment of lobs - vacancy, departmental work (includes notes, drafts & agreement & exhibits)
- Egg Harbor Boat Co. vs. IBT, Local 158, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Issue: classification of jobs - upgrading (includes notes, exhibits, agreements & drafts)
- Eico Huntingdon Corp. vs. IBEW, Lodge No. 2099, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  Issue: failure to call-in (includes agreement, notes, briefs, newspapers)
- Electric AutoLite Co. Cases, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Electric Storage Battery Co., Inc. vs. Battery Workers. Union, Local 113, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  Issue: discipline -suspension.
- Eljer Co., Division of Hurray Corp. of America vs. United Glass & Ceramic Workers of North America & Eljer Local No. 158, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Issue: rates of pay -defective work.
- Emmons Foundry & Machinery Co. vs. Eastern PA. Conference Board of the Int'l. Holders & Allied Workers, Local 18, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Issue: rates of pay -transfers.
- Employing Bricklayers Assoc. of Delaware Valley vs. Bricklayers Locals, 1961-1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Issue: rates of pay; discipline - discharge.
- Ervin Hills, Inc. vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Locals, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  6/8/65. Issue: discipline warnings, discharge
- Eureka Division, Little Industries vs. Int'l. Bro. of Bookbinders, Local 97, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Issue: recall -method of recall.
- Evans, John R. & Co. vs. Int'l. Fur & Leather Workers Union, Local 206, 1948-1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Issue: layoff -vacation pay; termination of employment - inability.
- 1948-1955 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Evening Star Broadcasting Co. vs. Nat'l. Assoc. of Broadcast Employees & Technicians, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Issue: automation - equipment change.
- Evening Star Newspaper Co. vs. Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Extrudo Film Corp. vs. OCAW, Minersville Local 8-179, 1965-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Issue: transfers - rates of pay; contracting out.
- 1965-1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Exxon Co. vs. Esso Industrial Employees Assoc, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Issue: arbitrability - timeliness.
- Fabricon Products, a division of Eagle-Picher Industries, Inc. vs. Int'l. Printing Pressmen & Assistants Union, Locals 4-11, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Fairchild Aircraft Division vs. UAW, Local 842, 1957-1960 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Issue: shift preference bumping; classification of jobs; management rights.
- Fernwood Co. vs. Amalgamated Food Employers, Local 196, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Issue: vacations; vacation pay; rates of pay; overtime - remedy for improper assignment.
- Fidelity Electric Co. vs. Int'l. Union of Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers, CIO, Coal 121 (IUE), 1955 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Issue: vacations - computation.
- Fischer & Porter Co. vs. Independent Union of Rotometer Workers, 1967-1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - ability vs. seniority; discipline - discharge.
- Flexsteel Industries, Inc. vs. Upholsterers Int'l. Union of H.A., Local 180, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Issue: rates of pay - red-circle rates.
- Food Fair Stores, Inc. Cases, 1964-1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Food Fair Stores, Inc. Cases, 1964-1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Foodarama Shop Rite vs. Retail Clerks Int'l., Retail Store Employees Union, Local 1262, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Issue: termination of employment - discharge vs. quits.
- Foster Wheeler Corp. vs. IBBISBFH, Local 159, 1955-1962 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Issue: discipline discharge; overtime.
- Franklin Balmar Division, Hacrodyne-Chatillon Corp. vs. Aim, Lodge 211, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Issue: fringe benefits - retirees.
- Franklin Lakes Market, Inc. vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 1262, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Issue: layoffs - super seniority.
- Franklin Smelting & Refining Co. vs. USW, Local 4254, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Issue: termination of employment - discharge vs. quits; demotion.
- Freihofer, William Baking Co. vs. Truck Drivers & Helpers Union, Local 676, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- French, R.T. Co. vs. IAM, District Lodge #1, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  Issue: working conditions.
- Frommeyer & Co. vs. MB&PIU of America; vs. Bricklayers Union #1 of PA, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Fruehauf Corp. vs. Int'l. Union Allied Industrial Workers, Local 488, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Fuller Co. vs. Int'l. Molders & Allied Workers, Local 287, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime; transfers, temporary.
- G-L Electronics Co, Inc. vs. IUE #134, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Issue: overtime - rate of pay, vacancy - assignment of jobs.
- General American Transportation Corp. vs. Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers. Int'l. Union #8, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Issue: overtime, failure to schedule.
- General Battery & Ceramic Corp. vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Issue: discipline - discharge. (no decision, only notes)
- General Building Contractors Association vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, Metropolitan Dist. Council, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Issue: discipline - discharge (work breaks)
- General Cable Corporation vs. IBEW #868, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Issue: call-in - improper assignment of work.
- General Dynamics Corp., Liquid Carbonic Division vs. Oil, Chemical, & Atomic Workers Int'l. Union, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Issue: shift scheduling - change of schedule; classification of jobs assignment of work outside of classification.
- General Electric Co. vs. UERMWA, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- General Foam Corporation vs. UMWA # 50, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Issue: discipline (suspension - suspension) leaving plant without permission.
- Georgia-Pacific Corp. vs. United Papermakers & Paperworkers #526, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Issue: discipline - discharge (assault of fellow employees)
- Gindy Manufacturing Corp. vs. United Steelworkers of America #6180, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Issue: insurance - coverage.
- Glen Food Hart vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen of North America #195, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Issue: bumping - seniority.
- Globe Screen Printing Corp. vs. Printing Specialties & Paper Products Union #481, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Issue: discipline - discharge (excessive absence).
- Good Deal Supermarkets vs. Retail Store Employees Union #1262, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Gould Inc. Clevate Engine Parts Division vs. UAW #416, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Issue: fringe benefits (pension plans).
- Gould National Battery Co. vs. UERMWA, 1954-1959 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Issue: rate of pay. (guaranteed rate); bumping - seniority.
- The Grand Union Co. vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 1262, 1966-1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Graver Tank & Manufacturing Co. vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Ironship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers & Helpers, Local 23, 1957-1964 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Issue: discipline/discharge (stoppage of work); lunch period rate of pay.
- Greene, Tweed & Co. Inc. vs. United Textile Workers of America, Local 31, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Issue: rate of pay.
- Greyhound Lines, Inc., Pennsylvania vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, Local 1210, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Issue: discipline/discharge (negligence).
- Ground Services Inc. vs. IAM, Local 41, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  Issue: discipline/discharge (employee theft).
- Guerin Special Motor Freight, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 500, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Gypsum Haulage, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 676, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  Issue: discipline/discharge (assault on fellow employee).
- Hadden Craftsmen Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 97, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  Issue: reporting pay/power failure.
- Hahnemann Hospital vs. National Union of Hospital & Health Care Employees, Local 1199, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  Issue: discipline - suspension; layoff seniority; discipline - discharge.
- Hamilton Rubber Manufacturing Corp. and Hamilton Paper Co. Cases, 1953-1961 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Harbisons Dairies vs. Food Driver Salesmen, Party & Ice Cream Workers Union, Local 463, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  Issue: discipline (discharge/negligence).
- United Gas Improvement Co., Harrisburg Gas Division vs. IBEW Local 1941, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  Issue: shift scheduling - rotating shifts (no decision).
- Harper-Theil vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5507, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  Issue: holiday pay/computation.
- Heil Co. vs. United Steel Workers of America, Local 6880, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  Issue: classification of jobs/rates of pay.
- Heil Co. vs. United Steel Workers of America, Local 6880, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Heil Co. vs. United Steel Workers of America, Local 6880, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- H.J. Heinz Co. vs. Amalgamated Foods & Allied Workers Union, Local 50, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  Issue: discipline/dismissal (personal appearance).
- Heintz Division, Kelsey-Hayes Co. vs. UAW, Local 834, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Hellertovn Manufacturing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1235, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  Issue: call-in/act of God.
- Herbery Hosiery Co. vs. American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  Issue: standards of production/workload; schedule of work/workweek.
- Hercules Cement Co. vs. United Cement, Lime & Gypsum Workers, Local 22, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  Issue: holidays/schedule of work; classification of job (assignment of work outside classification.
- Hershey Chocolate Corp. vs. American Bakery & Confectionary Workers, Local 464, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  Issue: schedules of work/shift scheduling.
- Hess Goldsmith & Co., Inc., Atwater Oil. and Hess Oil and Chemical Corp., 1955-1963 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Highway Trailer Industries Inc. vs. (JAW, Local 1026 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  Issue: discipline - suspension (wild cat strike).
- C.U. Hill Co. Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5298, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  Issue: discipline - discharge (violation of plant rules). No decision, notes only.
- Hinde & Ranch Division of West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. United Papermakers & Paperworkers, Local 358, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- H. H. Hollingsheud Corp. vs. Automotive Chemical Products Union, Local 22130, 1956-1968 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - crossing craft lines, overtime - failure to schedule.
- Hollingsvorth, John B. Co. vs. IBEW, Loci 1448, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  Issue: Assignment to work outside classification - past practice.
- Houghton, E.F. & Co. vs. Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers Int'l. Union, Local 8-398, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  Issue: vacations - illness during, effect.
- Hunt Wesson Foods, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Food & Allied Workers Union, Local 56, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  Issue: discipline/discharge (theft).
- Huntington Alloy Products Division, International Nickel Co., Local 40, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  Issue: discipline - discharge (assault on fellow employee).
- Hussman Refrigerator Company vs. United Industrial Workers of North America of the Seafarers' Int'l. Union of North America, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  Issue: management rights - unilateral action.
- Hyde, A.L. Co. vs. IBT, Local 676, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  Issue: strikes, slowdowns & work stoppages/work stoppages (no decisions included).
- I-T-E Imperial Corp. and UAW, Local 1612, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Issue: discharge - improper job attitude - no attempt at improvement (includes notes, exhibits, brief).
- ITT Nesbitt Co. and USW, Local 1385, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Issue: discipline - suspension (includes drafts, notes & exhibits).
- Individual Drinking Cup Co. and UPP, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Int'l. Nickel Co., Inc. vs. USW, Local 40, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Int'l. Paper Co., Levisberg Plant vs. United Paperworkers Int'l. Union, Local 1318, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Issue: bidding - ability vs. seniority.
- Haddon Coraftsnen, Inc. Div. of the Int'l. Textbook Co. vs. Int'l. Bro. of Bookbinders, Local 97, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Issue: discipline - suspension; excessive absences.
- J & H, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Food Employees Union, Local 590, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Issue: part-time employees -extended workweek pay. (includes transcript, drafts & exhibits).
- Jamestown Products Division of AVH Corp. vs. IAH, Lodge 2111, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Issue: overtime - equalization (includes notes, drafts & exhibits).
- Jeanette, City of vs. Jeanette Police, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Jetronic Industries, Inc. and USW, Local 4913, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Issue: sick leave - termination following leave; layoff holiday pay.
- Johns Hopkins Hospital vs. Nat'l. Union of Hospital & Nursing Homes Employees, Local 1199, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Issue: discharge - absence.
- Jones Motor Co. vs. Freight Drivers & Helpers, Local 557, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Issue: quit vs. discharge.
- Justi, H.D. & Son, Inc. vs. United Retail & Wholesale Employees, Local 115, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  Issue: reporting pay.
- Kaiser Metal Products, Inc. vs. UAW, Local 130, 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Issue: bumping qualifications, vacancies - bidding - seniority.
- Kavecki Berylco Industries, Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers Int'l. Union (OCAW) Local 8-837, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Issue: premium pay.
- Kaye-Tex Mfg. Co. Cases (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Keassey & Mattison Co. and United Textile Workers of America, Local 2409, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  Issue: discharge -insubordination.
- Keller Moving & Storage, Inc. vs. Teamsters, Local 773, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  Issue: overtime - failure to assign, (includes notes, exhibits, drafts).
- Kendall Co. vs. UTWA, Local 2014, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Kennametal, Inc. vs. UAW, Local 1059, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  Issue: bumping - layoff - demotion
- Kennedy Van Saun Corp. vs. Foundrymen, Machinists & Erectors Union, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  Issue: holiday pay.
- Keystone Lighting Corp. and IBEW, Local 1841, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Kieckhafer Container Corp. vs. Int'l. Bro. of Pulp, Sulphite & Paper Mill Workers., Local 380, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  Issue: discharge - time clock procedure - union employees.
- Koppers Co., Inc. Cases, 1968-1973 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Kovette Division, E.J., of Spartans Industries, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks, Local 1357, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  Issue: discharge - customer relations (includes notes, exhibits, drafts).
- Kraft Foods vs. Amalgamated Food & Allied Workers Union, Local 56, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Krill, Inc., George and Truck Drivers & Helpers Local 355, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  Issue: discharge -insubordination (includes notes, exhibits & drafts).
- Kutztovn Foundry & Machine Corp. vs. Int'l. Holders & Allied Workers Union, Local 1361, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Labor Standards Ass'n. Cases, 1956-1968 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  Issue: rates of pay wage reopener; change of schedule.
- Lachman Co., Charles Cases, 1959-1968 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Lansford Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  Issue: incentive pay (piece rate).
- Lasko Metal Products, Inc. vs. UAW, Local 1438, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  Issue: quit, seniority; claim for pay of a higher classification.
- Latrobe Steel Co. vs. USW, Local 1537, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  Issue: 1) schedules of work - change - overtime 2) premium pay 3) subcontracting (includes briefs, notes, drafts & exhibits).
- Lavine & Co., E.J. vs. USA, Local 3283, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  Issues: 1) failure to call-in 2) failure to call-in - seniority 3) failure to assign - seniority 4) failure to assign.
- Lawrence Hose Co., vs. TWVA, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  Issue: discharge - gambling.
- Leaman Transportation Corp. vs. IBT, Local 312, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  Issue: holiday pay - eligibility.
- Lebanon Steel Foundry vs. USW, Local 1975, 1958-1961 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Leeds & Northrup Co. vs. Leed & Northrup Employees Union; vs. UAW Local 1350, 1966-1976 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  . 5/4/66. Issue: discipline - suspension -absence notice; discharge - unsatisfactory
- Lehigh Portland Cement Co. vs. IBT, Local 773, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  Issue: discharge - accident.
- Lehigh Structural Steel Co. vs. Int'l. Ass'n. of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers., AFL-CIO, Shipman's Local Union 548, 1956-1964 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  1) 5/15/56. Issue: layoff - temporary - compensation. 2) 9/30/58. Issue: discharge - insubordination. 3) 6/24/59. Issue: layoff - lack of work - seniority. 4) 9/14/60. Issue: temporary assignment, reduction in wages, failure to assign. 5) 12/7/64. Issue:
- Lehigh Valley Dairies, Sealtest Foods & Abbotts Dairies vs. IBT, Local 676, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  Issue: birthday holiday - strike - discrimination (includes draft, exhibits, briefs).
- Lenape Forge, Div. of Bonney Forge & Foundry, Inc. vs. USW, Local 7207, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  Issue: transfer -mgt. rts. (includes exhibits, notes, drafts, briefs).
- LeStourgen Baking Co. vs. Independent Bakers Union, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Levitz Furniture of Allentown, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks & Store Employees Union, Local 1361, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  Issue: discharge - union activities.
- Liquid Carbonic Corp. vs. Int'l. Bro. of Firemen & Oilers, Local 473, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  Issue: discharge -neglect, plant rules in general (includes notes, exhibits, draft).
- Link - Belt Co. Cases, 1947-1964 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  Issue: rates of pay rate revision; sub-contracting.
- Linton's Lunch, Inc. vs. Restaurant Guild Chain Store Employee's Alliance, Local 138, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Lit Brothers vs. Retail Clerks Int'l. Assoc., Local 1390, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Issue: contracting out - bargaining unit work.
- Litho-Strip Corp. vs. UAW, Local 181, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Issue: management rights - work week reduction.
- Lukens Steel Co. vs. USW, Local 1165, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Issue: apprentices, learners & trainees - testing
- Lummis & Co. Cases, 1958-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Issue: discrimination; discipline discharge.
- Luria Engineering Co. vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 594, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Issue: promotions - testing.
- Lycoming Division - Avco Corp. vs. UAW, 1954-1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Issue: discipline.
- Hack Manufacturing Corp. vs. UAW, Local 677, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Issue: reinstatement.
- Macke Variety Vending Co. vs. United Class & Ceramic Workers of N.A., Local 423, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Martin. L. Co., Inc. vs. UMW, Local 12092, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority.
- Martin's Wholesale City, Rite Aid Corp. vs. Retail Clerks Union, Local 1357, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Master Plasterers Co. of Philadelphia & Lathing & Plastering Contractors Assoc. of Philadelphia, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Issue: contract interpretation -determination of meaning.
- Matthey Bishop, Inc. vs. USW, Local 3183, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Issue: contracting out - contract silence.
- Maxson, W.L. Corp. vs. UAW, Local 1221, 1954-1964 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  1) Issue: discipline - warnings; discipline -suspensions. 2) Issue: classification of jobs - location of machinery; rates of pay. 3) Issue: rates of pay. 4) Issue: assignment of jobs - recall. 5) Issue: assignment of jobs - recall. 6) Issue: assignme
- McAllister, D.F. & Sons vs. Waiters & Waitresses Union, Local 301, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- McNichol, D.J. Co. vs. IBT, Food Drivers, Helpers & Warehousemen, Local 500, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Merchant Warehouse Co. vs. IBT, Local 161, Transportation Checkers, Receivers & Clerical Workers, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  Issue: union security - union shop.
- Merck & Co., Inc. Cases, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Merck & Co., Inc. Cases; Methacton School District vs. Methacton Education Association, 1966-1973 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  Issue: assignment of jobs; rates of pay.
- Met-pro Systems Division vs. UAW, Local 416, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Issue: recall - seniority.
- Metropolitan Edison Co. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 603, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  Issue: promotions - failure to qualify.
- Mid-city Meats Co., Inc. vs. Amalgamated Food Employees, Local 196, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Midland Glass Co., Inc. vs. Glass Bottle Blowers Assoc. (GBBA) Local 119, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  Issue: shutdown -holidays & holiday pay
- Milprint, Inc. Cases, 1968-1976 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  Issue: strikes, slowdowns & Stoppages; sick leave and sick pay.
- Minnesota Mining & Manufacturing Co. Cases, 1957-1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- 1Midvale Co. vs. Federal Labor Union No. 18687, AF of L, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  Issue: strikes, slowdowns & work stoppages - vacation pay computation.
- Mohawk Devices, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1841, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Monongahela, City of vs. Monongahela Police, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  Issue: contract modification - wage adjustments - holidays.
- Monsanto Co., Yardville Plant vs. UGCW, Local 439, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  Issue: discipline - warnings.
- Montgomery Sylvania Mfg. Co. - Jersey Shore Sylvania Mfg. Co. vs. Int'l. Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Local 306, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  Issue: contract interpretation -effective date.
- 1Monterey Coal Co. vs. UMW, Dist. 12, Local 1613, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - De Minimus assignments.
- Morrell-Felin Co. vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen of N.A., Local 195, 1961-1966 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  1) Issue: discipline - discharge. 2) Issue: discipline - suspension. 3) Issue: bumping - seniority.
- Morysville Body Works, Inc. s. USW, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  Issue: bumping - layoff.
- Nt. Holly, N.J. Shop-rite vs. Retail Clerks, Local 1360, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Nat'l. Automatic Sprinkler & Fire Control Assoc. vs. Sprinkler Fitters Local #692, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Issue: contract modification - wage adjustments
- National Broadcasting Co., Inc. vs. Int'l. Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees & Moving Picture Machine Operators of the US & Can., Local 804 (IATSE), 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)